不敢相信，我以為這會很容易
I can't believe that I thought it'd be easy
我想，沒人是完美
Well I guess that no one's perfect
我被所謂的作夢給欺騙
I was deceived by a thing we call dreamin'
因為，我想一夢不醒
'Cause I thought I couldn't hurt it
現在看看我，是不是很清晰
Now look at me, it's so easy to see
有什麼在隱藏我所求
Something's hidin' what I asked for
歲月飛去
It's been years now
而我還才漸漸知道
And I'm still seekin' it out
也許，我是卡那在
Maybe I'm only stuck
自己，的那片雲上
on my own cloud above
也許沒怎樣
Maybe it's okay
也許我瘋狂
maybe I'm insane
也許它就是得這麼艱難
Maybe it's meant to be so tough
喔... 也許，我只是需要愛
Ohhhhh, or maybe all I need is love
我只是需要愛
All I need is love
我只是需要...
All I need is...
又一次，我感覺漸漸褪色
Once again, I can feel myself fadin'
我感覺多了一條新生命
I see a new life being colored in
我知道，我心不想痛下去
I can tell that my heart is done achin'
不知我是否多了層臉皮
But I wonder if I've gained another skin
我阻止不了這般轉變
I can't stop this transformation
奇怪的感覺帶我上天飛
An odd sensation's takin' me for a ride
一路飛到我心裡
All the way back through my mind
也許，我是卡那在
Maybe I'm only stuck
自己，的那片雲上
on my own cloud above
也許沒怎樣
Maybe it's okay
也許我瘋狂
maybe I'm insane
也許它就是得這麼艱難
Maybe it's meant to be so tough
喔... 也許，我只是需要愛
Ohhhhh, or maybe all I need is love
我只是需要愛
All I need is love
我只是需要...
All I need is...
愛
Love
也許，我是卡那在
Maybe I'm only stuck
自己，的那片雲上
on my own cloud above
也許沒怎樣
Maybe it's okay
也許我瘋狂
maybe I'm insane
也許它就是得這麼艱難
Maybe it's meant to be so tough
喔... 也許，我只是需要...
Ohhhhh, or maybe all I need is...
愛
love